# Ashton A. Westrick

# **Professional Summary**

I am a high school student with a passion for technology and creation. I have experience with leading and communication with children as well as an adept understanding of programming and video game development. I am also willing to learn any languages required for any project and can do so swiftly.

#### **SKILLS**

- Adept with the Unity game engine
- Communicating ideas with a younger audience
- Problem solving
- Small team management
- Organizational Skills

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### St. John Neumann Catholic Church, Sunbury Ohio - SALT Leadership Team

April 2015 - PRESENT

 Worked with kids grades 5-8 in multiple different events ranging from summer camps to one night events. Responsibilities include: giving short talks, organizing and leading activities and games, and heading small group discussions.

**Delaware Area Career Center South Campus, Delaware Ohio** – Manager Of Lost Animations Video Game Design Team

November 2018 - January 2019

• Ensured the cohesion of a small game design team in a national competition, I created plans to keep production smooth and kept the rest of the team on task. I also proofread the team's code and communicated with judges to assure our game's quality.

**Delaware Area Career Center South Campus** — Delaware Area Career Center Ambassador

April 2019 - Present

 Toured local school districts and interacted with both potential students and parents, explaining what the career center is and sharing my experience there.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Olentangy High School, Delaware Ohio

August 2016 - May 2018

Olentangy Berlin High School, Delaware Ohio

Current GPA of 3.7

# Delaware Area Career Center, Delaware Ohio

August 2018 - May 2020

Application Development and Programming

## **AWARDS**

- Member of the National Technical Honors Society
- Nationally ranked top 20 in the Business Professionals of America software engineering competition.